{
	"queryList":[
		{
			"basicFront": "What Kansas City park, at 1,805 acres, is more than twice the size of Central Park in New York City?",
			"basicBack":"Swope Park",
			"clozeFront":"Swope Park, at 1,805 acres, is more than twice the size of Central Park in New York City.",
			"clozeBack":"Swope Park"
		}
		{
			"basicFront":
			"basicBack":
			"clozeFront":
			"clozeBack":
		}
		{
			"basicFront":
			"basicBack":
			"clozeFront":
			"clozeBack":
		}
		{
			"basicFront":
			"basicBack":
			"clozeFront":
			"clozeBack":
		}
		{
			"basicFront":
			"basicBack":
			"clozeFront":
			"clozeBack":
		}
	]
}